tvfplay.com 2015-11-12

# TVF Play

  * Privacy policy

## Privacy policy

In order to provide information and services to visitors and registered users (together referred to as Users) of its website http://tvplay.com/, http://tvfinboxoffice.com/ and its mobile application (together referred to as the Website), Contagious Online Media Network Private Limited (TVF) will, from time to time, collect, store, process and transfer certain personal information of the Users. This privacy policy (Privacy Policy) sets out the practices and policies followed by TVF in connection with the personal information and/or sensitive personal data or information that TVF may collect from Users. By using the website and/ or by providing your Information (as defined below), Users consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the website in accordance with this privacy policy, including but not limited to consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy, read together with the terms and conditions of the terms of use of the Website (Terms) constitutes a legal and binding agreement between the User and TVF and is enforceable under the laws of India. 

The Privacy Policy is subject to revisions at any time, as determined by TVF, without notice, and any such changes are effective immediately upon being posted on the Website; any use of the Website thereafter will be deemed to be an acceptance of these changes by the User. Users are strongly urged to read this Privacy Policy in its entirety and to periodically check this page to understand how modifications or revisions to this policy affects the use of their information. TVF shall not be responsible for any Userâ€™s failure to remain informed about such changes. 

The safety of User information is extremely important to us and this Privacy Policy defines Users rights in relation to the information the User provides TVF, and answers questions that the User's may have about the manner in which TVF collects, uses, stores and safeguards your information. Most importantly, this Privacy Policy will explain the following to you in some detail: 

1\. The type of information we collect  
2\. Why we are collecting this information  
3\. When and how we can use this information  
4\. The others (in addition to us) that will collect and retain the information  
5\. Who we will share this information with

### Types of information we collect

From users like you, we collect the following types of information (hereinafter collectively referred to as the Information):

(a) As a part of the sign-up process, we will collect 'personal information' such as name, email address, age, gender, address and contact details.

(b) In case of any transaction made to access content on the Website, we may collect 'sensitive personal information' such as credit\debit card details.Additionally, as a part of the sign-up process, we may also require you to create a password. You may note that We adopt reasonable security measures to protect Your password from being exposed or disclosed to anyone

(c) If you access or engage with the Website or Services associated with the Website through a social media service, we may collect your user ID or user name, any information you have permitted the social media service to share with us, and any information you have made public with the social media service.

(d) Other information that we may collect include browser information and your IP address, the messages and emails you send us and the comments posted or shared by you on the Website.

The Information that you provide us, will be stored and guarded by the following entity: 

Contagious Media Online Network Private Limited  
Flat No 503, Sameer Apartments, Versova Vipul Chs Ltd,  
Andheri West, Yari Road, Versova, Mumbai 400061.  
E-mail: admin@theviralfever.com 

### Why we collect, and how we use this Information

TVF uses the personal information collected from Users, for the provision of services to its Users.

The Users shall, at all times, have the option to refrain from disclosing their sensitive personal data or information to TVF. They shall also have the option of withdrawing consent previously provided to TVF. In all such cases, TVF shall no longer be obliged to provide the information and services as described on the Website or for which such data or information was sought. 

### Retention

TVF will not retain any sensitive personal data or information for longer than is required for the purpose for which such data or information was collected or may lawfully be used or is otherwise required under any other law for the time being in force. 

### Disclosure & Transfer

TVF will not publish or disclose your Information unless we really have to. This means that the only time that TVF will share or disclose your Information is when â€“ (a) it is necessary for TVF to do so to provide User with the complete set of services on our Website; or (b) the law requires us to do so. 

If TVF shares or transfers your Information to any third party, TVF will ensure that such third party has in place the same, or higher levels of data protection that we have adopted. This means that even if the Information is transferred to another entity, it will remain secure. 

### Security Practices and Procedures

TVF has ensured the confidentiality and security of the personal information and sensitive personal information provided by Users by implementing comprehensive information security practices and standards as mandated by the Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules, 2011 (Privacy Rules).

### Incorrect information

User will, at all times, be given the option to review and correct any inaccurate, incorrect or incomplete information that has been provided by accessing profile option once logged in.

Users could also choose not to share information with TVF, but in such cases, TVF may not be able to provide access to the services on its Website.

### Grievance Officer

In accordance with the requirements under the Privacy Rules, the name and contact details of TVFâ€™s Grievance Officer is provided below: 

Gaurav Rungta â€“ gaurav@theviralfever.com

### Links to Other Websites

TVF may, on the Website, provide links to third-party websites, which may, in turn, collect personal information or sensitive personal information of the User. TVF has no responsibility or liability for the privacy standards, practices and policies implemented on such websites.
